https://totaleclipse4u.com/default/privacy/

Menu
Crimpers & Die SetsModular Plug CrimpersCoaxial CrimpersFiber Optic CrimpersElectrical/Industrial CrimpersSolar CrimpersSpecialty CrimpersHydraulic CrimpersHydraulic Crimper Dies Lunar Series Die SetsModular Plug DiesCoaxial DiesFiber Optic DiesElectrical/Industrial DiesSolar Terminal DiesSolar Series Die SetsCrimper FramesHydraulic ToolsHydraulic Knockout PunchesHydraulic Punch DiesHydraulic CrimpersHydraulic Crimper DiesHydraulic CuttersHolemakingKnockout PunchesKnockout Punch DiesCordless Drills & DriversHole Saws & Drill BitsPunchdown ToolsTools with BladesHandles OnlyBlades / HeadsScrewdrivers & BitsPro-Soft SeriesFlat BladePhillipsStar TipTri-WingPrecision DriversFlat BladePhillipsStar TipTriangleTri-WingHex SocketHex TipPozidrivPentalobeSetsBits1000V RatedPliers, Strippers, & CuttersPrecision Pliers & CuttersBent-NosedNeedle-NosedFlat-NosedDiagonalFlushRound NosedCombinationElectrical Pliers & CuttersWire StrippersCable StrippersCable CuttersKnives, Scissors & SawsPVC CuttersWrenches & SocketsPower ToolsCordless Drills & DriversGrinders & EngraversBattery Powered CuttersBatteries, Parts & AccessoriesDrill BitsTool Kits & CasesElectronics Tool KitsNetworking Tool KitsElectrical Tool KitsFiber Optics Tool KitsCoaxial Tool KitsGeneral Purpose Tool KitsCases, Bags & PouchesCompartment BoxesMagnification & LightingDesktop Inspection LampsFlashlights & HeadlampsVisor & MagnifiersReplacement Bulbs & PartsUnilite Portable LightingFlashlightsInspection / Work LightsHeadlampsVestsTest InstrumentsMultimetersDigital MultimetersAnalog MetersReplacement ProbesNetwork Cable TestersTone & Probe SetsTelecom ButtsetsTemp/Humidity MetersMisc. TestersProbes - OscilloscopeReceptacle TestersNon-Contact TestersMetal & Stud DetectorsFiber OpticsSoldering & AssemblySoldering StationsSoldering IronsDesolderingHeat Guns & Glue GunsHeat Shrink TubesESD Static ProtectionTweezersAids & AccessoriesBreadboardsEnclosuresPin ExtractorsPick-Up ToolsMini-VacuumsFiber Optic ToolsFiber Optic CrimpersFiber Optic StrippersFiber Optic Tool KitsFiber Optic AccessoriesFiber Test InstrumentsLapping FilmsWiring InstallationPush Pull Rods & TapesMeasuring ToolsCable TiesCable Tie ToolsCable Ties - Hook and LoopCable Ties - NylonPartsTapeConnectorsModular Plugs & SplicesModular PlugsSplices - TelecomCoaxialCoax - Crimp StyleCoax - Push OnCoax - Twist OnCompression F ConnectorsCompression RCA ConnectorsCompression BNC ConnectorsSplittersWire FerrulesUninsulatedInsulatedTwin InsulatedWire TerminalsUninsulated Ring TerminalsInsulated Ring TerminalsClosed End ConnectorsButt SplicesFemale Disconnects (Push-Ons)Spade TerminalsLocking Spade Terminals
Account
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Last modified: August 21st, 2018.
The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to be clear on how Eclipse Enterprises (Eclipse Tools) collects, uses, and shares information about you through our websites and mobile applications that are owned and controlled by Eclipse Tools. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect your information.
What users of this Site can do if privacy policy is not upheld.
Information Collection, Use and Sharing
Releasing personal identifiable information is not required for you to use this site. However, you may not be able to use certain features and functions of this site such as signing up for newsletters or account registration. Required information to register for full access to this Site’s functionalities may include: your name, username, address or other contact, billing, or shipment information, email address, telephone number, along with any other personal information you choose to provide.
We will use this information to respond to you regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Some information we collect may not be personally identifiable based on how you navigate this Site. This may include: your IP address, browser type, computer or device identifiers, operating system version, the website from where you navigated to our Site, time and date of using our Site, the pages on our Site that you view, the name of your Internet service provider (ISP), and location information.
We use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”) to collect non-identifiable information based on the use of our Site (including your IP address). Google Analytics uses “cookies” to analyze how users use this Site. The information generated will be stored by Google on servers in the United States. You may opt-out of cookies use by adjusting the settings in your browser. Please note that if you do refuse the use of cookies, you may not be able to use this Site fully. For more information about Google Analytics you can visit Google’s website.
Wherever we collect sensitive information such as credit card date for example, that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You will see a lock icon in the address bar to verify along with an “https” at the beginning of the address of the Web page.
We also protect your information offline. Only Eclipse Tools Staff who need the information to perform their specific job duties are authorized to access personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
If you have any questions or concerns regarding our Privacy Notice please contact us immediately at (804) 561-2610 or email us.
